<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
<title>The Nonsense Buffer</title>
<link>https://thisiskarthik.com</link>
<description>Writings and observations by Karthik</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:43:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<atom:link href="https://thisiskarthik.comrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[So, I went to see cricket for the first time]]></title>
<link>https://thisiskarthik.com/writings/so-i-went-to-see-cricket-for-the-first-time</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://thisiskarthik.com/writings/so-i-went-to-see-cricket-for-the-first-time</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Cricket in India is insane, too famous for its own good, really. I had always wanted to watch cricket live, but I never knew how. For the longest time, I genuinely believed you needed to know someone, someone who knows someone, to get a ticket. Apparently not, at least not for this World Cup, thanks to the ICC. 
 I simply opened BookMyShow, selected my seats, paid via UPI, and voila, just like that, I had a confirmed ticket to watch my first ever cricket match at Chepauk. Who was playing? No ide...]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[The year of the linux desktop is here, old man!]]></title>
<link>https://thisiskarthik.com/writings/the-year-of-the-linux-desktop-is-here-old-man</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://thisiskarthik.com/writings/the-year-of-the-linux-desktop-is-here-old-man</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[For a very long time, I thought I was bad at making choices. 
 Not the big dramatic life choices... but the ones like choosing an operating system. 
 I say this because I spent an unreasonable amount of time deciding between operating systems that, on paper, all do the same thing. In reality, though, they follow very different philosophies. At some point, it even feels like you’re picking a religion. 
 Windows was my first operating system. More specifically, it was Windows 2000. My memories o...]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[That's it, I'm done with smartwatches]]></title>
<link>https://thisiskarthik.com/writings/thats-it-im-done-with-smartwatches</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://thisiskarthik.com/writings/thats-it-im-done-with-smartwatches</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[I loved watches as a kid, which is a bit ironic considering I didn't actually own a single one until I was halfway through the 8th grade. My grandmother finally ended that long streak by gifting me a Titan Zoop, which was one of those analog quartz watches designed specifically for children. It had a tiny dial and a light blue strap, but the most confusing part was a second, darker blue back strap that was supposedly there for &quot;support&quot;. 
 I honestly hated wearing that thing because it...]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>