<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
<title>Hmm... Blog?</title>
<link>https://thisiskarthik.com</link>
<description>Writings and observations by Karthik</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:13:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<atom:link href="https://thisiskarthik.comrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[The year of the linux desktop is here, old man!]]></title>
<link>https://thisiskarthik.com/writings/the-year-of-the-linux-desktop-is-here-old-man</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://thisiskarthik.com/writings/the-year-of-the-linux-desktop-is-here-old-man</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[For a very long time, I thought I was bad at making choices. 
 Not the big dramatic life choices... but the ones like choosing an operating system. 
 I say this because I spent an unreasonable amount of time deciding between operating systems that, on paper, all do the same thing. In reality, though, they follow very different philosophies. At some point, it even feels like you’re picking a religion. 
 Windows was my first operating system. More specifically, it was Windows 2000. My memories o...]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[I imagined a WhatsApp message across the world]]></title>
<link>https://thisiskarthik.com/writings/i-imagined-a-whatsapp-message-across-the-world</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://thisiskarthik.com/writings/i-imagined-a-whatsapp-message-across-the-world</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[I had too much free time the other day (always dangerous), so instead of doing something useful, I got curious about what actually happens when I send a WhatsApp message from Bangalore to someone in San Francisco. Just a simple &quot;Hi&quot;. So I tried to trace the journey. I made some assumptions along the way, but hey, the whole internet is basically built on assumptions anyway. 
 I'm in Bangalore (okay fine, I'm actually in Chennai, but let's pretend I'm in Bangalore for this story). I type...]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[That's it. I'm done with smartwatches!]]></title>
<link>https://thisiskarthik.com/writings/thats-it-im-done-with-smartwatches</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://thisiskarthik.com/writings/thats-it-im-done-with-smartwatches</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[As a kid, I loved watches. I didn’t own many. Actually, I didn’t own any at all until 8th grade, when my grandmother gifted me my first one. It was a Titan Zoop. One of those kids' analog quartz watches. Small dial. Light blue strap. Thin enough to disappear on my wrist. There was also a darker blue back strap for “support”, though I never quite understood what exactly it was supporting. 
 I hated wearing it. It looked delicate. Almost decorative. Meanwhile, my friends had watches with s...]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>